https://www.marchinglinks.com/Info/Privacy/privacy.html

New Items »
OneStopBandShop
Directors Showcase
Dinkles
Starline Baton
Used Uniforms »
Uniforms For Rent
Info »
Marching Bands
List Your Uniforms »
FAQs
Support
Privacy Policy
What This Privacy Policy CoversThis policy covers how MarchingLinks.com treats personal information that MarchingLinks.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of MarchingLinks.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number and that is not otherwise publicly available.This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MarchingLinks.com does not own or control, or to people that MarchingLinks.com does not employ or manage.Information Collection and UseIn general, MarchingLinks.com collects personal information when you register with MarchingLinks.com, when you use MarchingLinks.com products or services, when you visit MarchingLinks.com pages or the pages of certain MarchingLinks.com partners and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. MarchingLinks.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address,  occupation, industry and personal interests. Once you register with MarchingLinks.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.MarchingLinks.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.MarchingLinks.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, MarchingLinks.com cookie information, and the page you request.MarchingLinks.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.Information Sharing and DisclosureMarchingLinks.com does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission or under the following circumstances:We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MarchingLinks.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help MarchingLinks.com communicate with you about offers from MarchingLinks.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MarchingLinks.com’s terms of use or as otherwise required by law.We transfer information about you if MarchingLinks.com is acquired by or merged with another company. MarchingLinks.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.MarchingLinks.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.MarchingLinks.com advertisers include companies (such as stores, airlines and software companies).CookiesMarchingLinks.com may set and access MarchingLinks.com cookies on your computer.MarchingLinks.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MarchingLinks.com’s cookies.MarchingLinks.com uses web beacons to access MarchingLinks.com cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with MarchingLinks.com products and services.Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and PreferencesGeneralWe reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MarchingLinks.com service such as service announcements, administrative messages and The MarchingLinks.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your MarchingLinks.com account.  Confidentiality and SecurityWe limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your MarchingLinks.com Account Information is password-protected.In certain areas MarchingLinks.com uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.Changes to this Privacy PolicyMarchingLinks.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MarchingLinks.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
MarchingLinks.com ©
| All Rights Reserved
Template Design by RTBWizards.com
